question_data = [
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"category": "General Knowledge",
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
}
]
